startups.co 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Startups.co

The privacy of Startups.co Network users and their information is extremely important to Startups.co and we take this matter very seriously. All users of the Startups.co Network are covered by the following Privacy Policy. The Startups.co Network reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy. If required to do so, or it is in our best interest, Startups.co may release user information in compliance with law enforcement agencies.

In order to secure your personal information, all communications between you and the Startups.co Network website are secured. Furthermore, your personal information cannot be accessed by other users. Therefore, other users will never be able to see this private information. Moreover, Startups.co will never share your contact information with another user, unless requested to do so by you.

Persons under the age of 18 are prohibited from using the Startups.co Network and any associated services. These individuals are therefore not authorized to submit any private information to the system and Startups.co accepts no liability for such actions. 

###  The Startups.co Network

The Startups.co Network is an online service that allows business professionals to connect and interact with one another. Users are represented on the site with personal profiles. You choose the information in your profile and therefore control what can be seen by other users. The Startups.co Network must collect certain pieces of information in the normal course of its business and Startups.co retains the ownership rights to this information.

###  Primary Information Types

There are several primary types of information that are collected including Contact, Profile, and Internet information. In the future, credit card information may also be accepted for membership fees and other services. Startups.co is in no way limited to the collection of only this type of information and may deem it necessary to collect other data. You will be notified if any changes are made to this policy via a posting on this website.

###  Contact Information

Upon registering as a Startups.co Network user, certain contact information such as your name, email address, and mailing address may be collected. This serves as an example and is not intended to be a complete list of information that may be collected at registration.

###  Profile

Following registration, Startups.co Network users will be prompted to complete a profile. Current users can also make changes to their own user profile. A user profile may contain, but is not limited to, your name, a personal statement, your work experience, goals, and any items contained on a resume. You should use good judgement about the information that you post in your profile since this can be viewed by others on the Startups.co Network. Your personal contact information CANNOT be viewed unless you release this information. Addtionally, the information in your profile can be edited at your discretion at any time.

###  Internet

As part of our efforts to provide better services to Startups.co Network users, Startups.co collects certain information related to the Internet and your computer. In order for us to analyze trends and provide superior service to our users, Startups.co retrieves the web address (URL) of both the website that you visited directly before and directly after visiting the Startups.co Network site. We also receive certain other information about your personal computer such as the unique IP address. Startups.co also follows a standard practice of using cookies and logs to analyze website usage. Cookies a extremely small files that are stored on your computer and help us to provide you with a better experience by automatically recalling your preferences each time you visit our site. Cookies will not harm your computer in any way and can be deleted at any time.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively you can point users to opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)
  * We use Remarketing Dynamic Ads, which uses the Teracent cookie. Users may opt out of the Teracent cookie by visiting the [Teracent opt-out page](http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out).

User Accounts

You may make changes to your Startups.co Network account and any associated preferences at any time. To make changes, you must log onto the Startups.co Network and make any edits through the My Startups.co section. You may also request to terminate your Startups.co account. To request a removal of your account, please contact us.

###  System Generated Emails

As part of the normal functioning of the Startups.co Network, users may receive email requests from Startups.co or for contact from other users. Additionally, Startups.co will send you system generated emails and promotional materials. These communications may begin during the registration process and continue while your account remains on the Startups.co Network. If you wish to opt out of promotional emails, please contact us and specify your request. You can adjust the frequency of emails that you receive by making these changes in the My Startups.co section of your account. 

###  Affiliate and Partner Services

We do intend to use a third party to verify and process credit card information for any fees or purchases made on the Startups.co Network or with Startups.co. All third parties are required to use your information in a secure manner and only for the purpose given to them and cannot store or release this information. Certain profile information, including contact information, may be released to our affiliates and partners for the purpose of marketing and improving our service to you.

If you have a question about this privacy policy, please contact us or write to us at:

Attn: Privacy Policy  
Startups.co.  
1322 Manning Pkwy  
Powell, Ohio 43065 USA
